# WEN WEN

CS Ph.D. Student

### **SUMMARY**

I am currently a Ph.D. student at City University of Hong Kong (CityU), working under the guidance of Prof. Kede Ma. Alongside my studies, I am also actively involved as a student researcher at ByteDance Multimedia Lab. My research primarily revolves around video quality assessment, aiming to develop innovative methods in this domain.

### **EDUCATION** -

08/2021 - present City University of Hong Kong

Ph.D., Computer Science

09/2019 - 06/2021 Sun Yat-sen University

M.A.Sc., Applied Statistics

09/2015 - 06/2019 Sun Yat-sen University

B.Sc., Statistics

2017 Fall University of California, Berkeley

Visiting Undergrad, Math

#### **PAPERS**

VOA Modular Blind Video Quality Assessment (CVPR2024)

Wen Wen, Mu Li, Yabin Zhang, Yiting Liao, Junlin Li, Li Zhang, and Kede Ma

Learned Scanpaths Aid Blind Panoramic Video Quality Assessment (CVPR2024) **VR VQA** 

Kanglong Fan, Wen Wen, Mu Li, Yifan Peng, and Kede Ma

Perceptual Quality Assessment of Virtual Reality Videos in the Wild (TCSVT) VR VQA

Wen Wen, Mu Li, Yiru Yao, Xiangjie Sui, Yabin Zhang, Long Lan, Yuming Fang, Kede Ma

## **WORKING PAPERS**

VQA

Analysis of Video Quality Datasets via Design of Minimalistic Video Quality Models

Wei Sun, Wen Wen, Xiongkuo Min, Long Lan, Guangtao Zhai, and Kede Ma

### EXPERIENCE -

05/2023 - present ByteDance Multimedia Lab

- · Student Researcher
- · Conducting research on video quality assessment.

### 12/2019 - 08/2020 Alibaba Cloud Industry Brain

- · Summer Intern
- · Worked as an algorithm engineer intern. Responsible for industry data analysis and automatic control technology. Produced one patent.

# 11/2018 - 05/2019 Guangfa Securities Information Technology Department

- · Summer Intern
- · Worked as an algorithm engineer intern. Responsible for recommendation algorithm. Produced one patent.

### SERVICES -

09/2021 - present CS4487 Machine Learning

Teaching Assistant

· Teaching Tutor